With sincere devotion, on April 8th, the year of Quy Mao (
với tâm thành kính ngày 8/4 năm Quý Mão
June 25th, 2023), Ms.
tức ngày 25 tháng 6 năm 2023 cô chủ
Pham Thi Yen, the club leader, along with the Buddhist followers
nhiệm Phạm Thị Yến đã cùng các phật tử
of the Golden Chrysanthemum Club, respectfully offered pure
trong câu lạc bộ cúc vàng đã cung kính
offerings and resources to the
rằng phẩm vật và tự tài thanh tịnh cúng
Venerable Monks who wished to observe the annual summer retreat
dường Chư Tôn Đức tăng nhân muốn an cư
at Trinh Pagoda, the
kiết hạ của Chư tăng tại chùa trình trụ
headquarters of the Vietnam Buddhist Association of
sở Giáo hội Phật giáo Việt Nam tỉnh
Quang Ninh Province.
Quảng Ninh
Every year, following the Buddha's teachings, the monks
Hàng năm theo lời Phật dạy Chư tăng lại
gather at the main monastic centers for the
Vân tập về các chốn Tùng Lâm chủ xứ để
summer retreat. During the three months of the summer retreat, the
cấm túc an cư kiết hạ Trung Tam Nguyệt
supreme Dharma is opened for the benefit of all beings,
khai vô thượng pháp bảo nhằm từ lợi lợi
for the benefit of humanity and the people. Following
tha làm lợi ích cho nhân thiên y cứ
the tradition of the summer retreat,
truyền thống an cư kiết hạ của tăng ni
this year the Buddhist monks of the province
năm nay Chư tăng Phật giáo tỉnh nhà đã
gathered at Trinh Pagoda for the
Vân tập về tại hạ trường Chùa trình để
three-month retreat, nine weeks of seclusion, worship, and prayer for
Tam Nguyệt An Cư Cửu tuần cấm túc hành
national peace and prosperity.
trì lễ bái cầu nguyện Quốc Thái dân an
We, the Buddhist followers, yearn for the blessings and merits of the Venerable Monks.
là phật tử chúng con khát bóng Vọng Cầu
We, the Buddhist followers, gather at the Dharma center for the
tử chúng con Đóng bè tạo Phúc Vân tập về
summer retreat at Trinh Pagoda, sincerely offering a
Đạo Tràng An Cư kiết hạ tại chùa trình
small amount of pure resources and offerings
thành tâm có chút tỉnh tài phẩm vật dâng
to support the merits of the
lên để cúng dường tùy hỷ công đức của
monks for three months.  In response to the
Chư tăng ba tháng an cư thể theo lời
request of the Buddhist followers, the monks have
thỉnh cầu của các phật tử Chư tăng đã tử
agreed and accepted the offerings,
vi hứa khả và Thọ nhận sự cúng dường
hoping that during the three-month rainy season retreat, the
nguyện mong trong 3 tháng an cư kiết hạ
monks will diligently practice for their own benefit and the
Chư tăng được tinh tấn tu hành tự lợi
benefit of others, bringing good to both humans and celestial beings, and that
lợi tha làm lợi ích cho nhân thiên mong
Buddhism will flourish, and all beings
cho Phật pháp được Hưng Thịnh chúng sinh
will be imbued with the Buddha's teachings, deeply believing in
được thấm nhuần lời Đức Phật dạy tin sâu
karma, cultivating virtuous minds, and achieving liberation.
nhân quả hướng thiện tâm giải thoát
[Music]
[âm nhạc]